death of the day that has passed
muerte del día que ha pasado
and there goes that they take away my salary and more
y va ahí que me quiten el sueldo y más
toxicity out and here we do not want
toxicidad fuera y aquí no queremos gente
toxic people 3 doritos after kfc can
tóxica 3 doritos después kfc puede
stay here the community manager is not
quedarse aquí el community manager no es
toxic at all what happened to dallas that does not
tóxico para nada qué pasó con dallas no
matter as a minimum example the rest
importa eso como ejemplo mínimo el resto
of his existence of free chicken to
de su existencia de pollo gratis a
blondes totally and still would not be
rubios totalmente y aún así no estaría
unemployed I tell you without paying well
parado te lo digo sin pagar bueno
guys in which you are seeing this
chavales en los que estáis viendo este
extract that I did not know what we are
extracto que no sabía de lo que estamos
talking about we are talking about the
hablando estamos hablando del extracto
previous extract okay blonde complains about coffees on
anterior vale rubio se queja de cafés en
the server and with all the reason in the
el servidor y con toda la razón del
world and it seems to me that they are making a
mundo y me parece que están haciendo el
fool of themselves and you know it is not worth it I have also
primo y lo sabes no vale también he
uploaded each main video or have you already
subido vídeo cada principal o ya habéis
seen the video of each main one the
visto el vídeo de cada principal el
video of the main channel today is the
vídeo del canal principal de hoy es la
[ __ ] the video of the main channel
[__] el vídeo del canal principal de
today although it is wrong for me to say it but it
hoy aunque esté mal que yo lo diga pero
is the support ok it is called and titled in
es la apoya ok se llama y se titula por
case you want to see it
si lo queréis ver
closing mouths michael jackson innocent
cerrando bocas michael jackson inocente
okay and I would like to share it
vale y me gustaría que lo compartiré
a lot I would like to share it is a
muchísimo me gustaría compartir es
lot because a very important video
muchísimo porque un vídeo muy importante
for all the funk where michael jackson
para todo el funk donde michael jackson
so more than apart from giving it a like
así que más que aparte de darle like
comment on other things I would appreciate it from the bottom of my
comentar otras cosas agradecería del
heart if you chose and the video you
corazón que escogiera y el vídeo
would share on facebook twitter
compartirás en facebook twitter en todas
everywhere okay well put it up being the
partes vale bueno lo pongáis siendo el
hot topic today has been that as not
tema fuerte de hoy ha sido que como no
Marbella you are going Marbella you are going again I don't
marbella vais marbella vais otra vez no
know why it has been organized as
sé por qué motivo se ha organizado como
an event that was like a battle of
un evento que era como de batalla de
roosters no and as not because of the fall of the
gallos no y como no por la caída del
dollar its worth a steak milestone there
dólar lo suyo vale un bife hito allí
gratuitously amateur is one less the whole
gratuitamente amateur es una menos todo
panorama you are a minor they are
el panorama tú eres una menor de edad
not going to call them galas as you can see it was
no se les van a llamar galas como veis
going to go how good it seemed to me let's say
iba a ir qué bueno me ha parecido
good let's say good to say that it did
digamos bien digamos bien por decir que
n't seem bad to me it was going to go like
no me ha parecido mal iba a irse que a
how she rushes and goes down like pure because she
como apura y baixa como pura porque se
was laughing in fact she was dancing the
estaba riendo de hecho estaba bailando
whole thing
todo el rollo
to excess but when he saw the situation he
a mayores pero cuando ha visto el percal
stood still as if to say I'm not
se ha quedado quieto como diciendo no
even going to blink because this clip is
voy ni a pestañear porque este clip se
going to go viral on twitter in 5
va a ser viral en twitter dentro de 5
minutes and now you and I here my face in
minutos y ahora tú y yo aquí mi cara en
the corner and once again more regrets the
la esquina y otra vez más lamentos los
fronts that I am throwing [ __ ] at her
frentes que yo estoy tirándole [__] la
okay so you were going to that it bothered  In
vale así que ibais a que incomodó en
this case it would not be a case of well it is in
este caso no sería caso de bien queda en
this case it would be a case of discomfort okay
este caso sería caso de incomodidad vale
because I was going to go it is really
porque iba a ir realmente le está
bothering him that this happened
incomodando que haya pasado esto
and not just KFC what happens with the
y no solo kfc punto que pasa con la
other brands
otras marcas
Repsol let's
repsol
see but it is different
a ver pero es diferente
as I explain it
como te explico
is different that maybe that would have been
es diferente que a lo mejor es que eso
good to put it briefly it is
hubiera sido bueno hablando corto es
different that the note seems to be seen
diferente que la nota parezca de ver
when an English cut as a joke
cuando un corte inglés como una gracia
that not everyone believes even if it is
que todo el mundo no creo aunque sea
advertising in itself I do not think that
publicidad en sí no creo que todo el
everyone is like the same as KFC
mundo lo es como lo mismo del kfc
understands the coffee is gaining a lot of
entiende el café se está ganando mucha
repercussion it is gaining there are brands that
repercusión está ganando hay marcas que
do not need advertising as such if
no necesitan publicidad como tal si
you had Coca-Cola
tuvieses cocacola
all the people like Coca-Cola they are going to
a toda la gente le gusta coca-cola va a
drink Coca-Cola and they are going to prefer to drink
tomar coca cola y va a preferir tomar
Coca-Cola before homemade that the homemade
coca cola antes que casera que la casera
cola understands me I mean there are brands that
de cola me entienda o sea hay marcas que
from my point of view do not need
desde mi punto de vista no necesitan
promotion as such to gain customers
promoción como tal para ganar clientela
okay then there are things that as they are
vale entonces hay cosas que como son
typical that we see on the street put as
típicas que vemos en la calle poner como
a promo as such although yes but it is the
una promo como tal aunque sí pero es lo
same it is not comparable it is not comparable
mismo no es comparable no es comparable
if mister ego the one who is singing
si el míster ego el que está cantando
this mister ego okay  already for sale
esto mister ego vale ya la venta queda
doctorate
doctorado
but I don't know what I'm going to do I want
pero yo no sé lo que voy a hacer quiero
the writers of a country I also want
los escritores de un país también quiero
the total what I was going to say I was a
los del total que iba a decir tenía un
little uncomfortable because the truth is
poco incómodo porque la verdad la
caught on camera and here in this explain he
pillada en cámara y aquí en esto explica
sent me it seems that the turkey
me haya mandado se ve que el pavo ya de
is already the typical oil I quote there is no
por sí es el típico aceite citó no hay
ter I quote that he has the habit of making
ter citó que tiene como costumbre hacer
these types of jokes that are actually
este tipo de bromas que en realidad son
accusations okay false accusations
acusación vale acusaciones falsas
Dallas it makes me bitter man to read it and
dallas me amarga macho el leerle y
get angry I had no
ponerme de mala leche yo no tenía ni
idea who this mystery was
idea de quién era este tal misterio
until this moment in Dallas stinks in the
hasta este momento en dallas apesta en a
crotch of a stork
entrepierna de cigüeña
these are typical comments that were
estos son típicos comentarios que se
made in 2018 2017 to be accepted
hacían en 2018 2017 para ser aceptado
to win from twyla edit them kf at that
para ganar de twyla editarlos kf ese
moment but it's not relevant but I
momento pero no viene al caso pero
need your opinion what do you think of Dallas you
necesito tu opinión qué opinas de dallas
suck son of a [ __ ] he's going to block you in a
apestas hijo [__] te va a bloquear en
matter of minutes gaga host [ __ ]
cuestión de minutos a gaga [__] [__]
what what what things no
qué que qué cosas no
matter honey thanks you are not going to be
vale cariño que gracias no se te va a
blocked in a matter of minutes watch out
bloquear en cuestión de minutos ojo es
the guy blocks a lot it's not very rare
que el tío bloquea mucho no es muy raro
for someone to block you and him  he says
que alguien te bloques y le dice por
all over your face you stink son of a [ __ ] no
toda la cara apestas hijo [__] no
better he's AIDS of my tl what he doesn't
mejor es un sida de mi tl lo que no
understand is that he sees in his girlfriends or the same
entiende que le ve en sus novias o igual
or they are equally healthy so
o son igual de sanos as
what a lack of respect here for free to
qué falta de respeto gratuitamente aquí
all the girlfriends not so much to Ingrid
a todas las novias no tanto a ingrid
as I will do like to Lis and that the current one does
como me haré como a lis y que el actual
not show disrespect
no se hace falta de respeto
and how these are to be from 2017 2018 2019
y como estos son to be de 2017 2018 2019
and as a note I hate people who throw
y como apunte odio a la gente que tira
firecrackers I hate Dallas which is very
petardos odio a dallas que es muy
tiring or from the wiki blah blah blah blah he
cansino o del wiki bla bla bla bla
says he hates hypocrisy
dice odia la hipocresía
okay to stay with this hate
vale quedar con esto de odio la
hypocrisy is to stay with these Dallas
hipocresía es quedar con éstos dallas
matters from vid go two to not
importa de vid vaya dos para no lija
minor sandpaper to not lose the habit of 0
menor para no perder la costumbre del 0
to Dallas how many things
al dallas cuanto a cosas
is he singing with his sister and this disgusts you
está cantando con su hermana y esto a ti
no no it disgusts me da la I don't know if it was a
no no me da asco da la no sé si ha sido
failure of expression and purchase and I
fallo de expresión y de compra y yo en
seriously put and compression with a
serio ha puesto y de compresión con una
gelatin
gelatina
my mother the level not
madre mía el nivel no
you and I only like Dallas and the abuse  from
tú y yo solo como dallas y el abuso de
his school we are just as disgusting but one
su colegio damos el mismo asco pero uno
has more followers
tiene más seguidores
anyway we see that it is a bit typical of
en fin vemos que es un poco típico de
this kid here we have a tweet
este chaval aquí tenemos un tuit
that says those who complain that we
que dice los que se quejan de que
do battles in Marbella by it is
hacemos batallas en marbella by es
because they are not in chin by
porque no están en barbilla by
gosh I do not understand this I do not understand
recórcholis no entiendo esto no entiendo
here Pepa begins to answer who is
aquí se pone a contestar la [__] que es
a non-extractive follower pep ducky
una seguidora no extractiva pep agache
as if telling her that although she has
como diciéndole que aunque ha
investigated a lot she does not see he is inspector
investigado mucho no ve es el inspector
gadget one day he had a boyfriend she met him in
gadget un día tuvo novio lo conoció en
habbo hotel they said silly a couple of times
habbo hotel dijeron boba un par de veces
they were banned the kid was hs twitter to
fueron baneado el niño era hs twitter a
his magic
su magia
is his character in 321 I saw close it is
es su personaje en 321 vi cerca da
very funny the guy who he
muchísima gracia el tipo que él en
really thinks he is doing died
realidad piensa que está haciendo murió
with it is your relationship with turbo in out
con la es tu relación con turbo in out
hero
héroe
well with now ternada 0 although not
pues bueno con now ternada 0 aunque no
the problem is over at least
ya se acabó el problema por lo menos
for me the problem we had is over
para mí se acabó el problema que tuvimos
each one to his own ball
cada uno a su bola
a certain respect that we do not mess
un cierto respeto que no nos metemos el
with each other I hope
uno con el otro espero
and with turbo very
y con turbo bien
little but look today he precisely sent me
poca pero mira hoy precisamente me puso
a message on instagram but a little
un mensaje en instagram pero una poca
thing a message but not a close relationship
cosa un mensaje pero no una relación
what the [ __ ] I do not know what to say  but well I
qué [__] no sé qué decir pero bueno me
imagine that like all humor no
imagino que como todos humor no
Alejandro in 2014 you do not educate yourself you do not
alejandro en 2014 tú no te educ tú no te
sleep with your wallet so you get into
me duerme con la cartera así te metes en
his account and there are videos of a priest very in
su cuenta y hay vídeos de cura muy
line with my mentions Dallas
acorde a mi menciona dallas
or in other words what he is comparing
o sea lo que está comparando
retweet of Dallas and retro and agent of
retweet de dallas y retro y agente de
flag to man of course he is
banderita a hombre claro que él está en
against the people of flag that the
contra de la gente de banderita que la
flag people I imagine he is
gente banderita me imagino que se
referring to right-wing people no
refiere a gente de derechas no
the character does not know
el personaje no sabe
jq thank you very much thank you very much
jq muchas gracias muchísimas gracias
the myth Marbella once every three
el mito marbella una vez cada tres
weeks go to the tall grass and get lost
semanas ve a la hierba alta y piérdete
here the gossip youtuber or you with the
aquí el chisme youtuber o tú con la
bag you already rule more than you think how
bolsa ya reglas más de lo que piensas
intelligent the humor
que inteligente el humor
well everyone is already disappointed some
bueno ya están todos despechados algún
bread visited more wants to go through his
pan visitó más quiere pasar por su
ration of [ __ ] start killing it
ración de [__] pónganse a matar que
seems that he has posted the photo of all of you
parece que os ha puesto la foto a todos
to moan and his name is
a gime y se llama
or in other words look what he is doing
o sea mira lo que está haciendo
hits that I saw thank you very much
hits que vi muchísimas gracias
welcome he is messing with the
bienvenido se está metiendo con el
physique of the kids and look look he is
físico de los chavales y mira mira está
quoting the either  he is literally
citando los ya sea literalmente está
quoting them with the photo
citando los con la foto
of the kids making fun of their uncle's physique
de los chavales burlándose con su físico
when this man
cuando este hombre
could be the father of these kids no
podría ser el padre de estos chicos no
because this man who will have
porque este hombre que tendrá
look if interview with you is not
mira si entrevista con ti para no tiene
wasted has an interview with a
desperdicio tiene una entrevista con
guy
tiparraco
but let's see literally or in front of
pero vamos a ver literalmente o frente a
a person in your song
una persona en tu canción
what could you have said after
que podrías haber dicho después lo
sorry I didn't know if you've been throwing [ __ ] at him for years he will
siento no sabía si llevas años tirándole
know more or less where the
[__] sabrá más o menos que las
accusations go and so on
acusaciones por dónde van y demás no
but they throw you throw [ __ ] at an
pero le tiran le tiras [__] a una
accusation of minors to a kid who has
acusación de menores a un chaval que a
n't done anything to you in his life
ti no te ha hecho nada en la vida
in Marbella vai and when people come
en marbella vai y cuando viene la gente
to tell you that this is wrong you start
a decirte que eso está mal te pones a
exposing them on your account making fun of his
exponerlos en tu cuenta burlándose de su
physique
físico
this is not 2017 my brain
esto no es 2017 mi cerebro
making fun of that irrefutable proof video
burlándose de que video de prueba
now he will put some tweet
irrefutable ahora pondrá algún tweet
saying with many ads
diciendo con muchos anuncios
this is no longer 2017 churra
esto ya no 2017 churra
diana 11 years old you have more photos of dallas
diana 11 años tienes más fotos de dallas
on his account than with his family his
en su cuenta que con su familia su
family is dallas but remember diana
familia es dallas pero recuerda diana
you are 11 years old
tienes 11 años
my mother and this man stops to
madre mía y se para este hombre a
answer one by  one to all of you who
contestar uno por uno a todos los que le
are putting you
están poniendo tú
here I don't want toxicity and here he
aquí no quiero toxicidad y aquí lo
invites him to mystery well I hope so well I'm
invita a misterio bueno espero que bueno
going to ask for explanations there is here
voy a pedirles explicaciones hay aquí
regarding this no hey guys he
respecto a esto no oye chavales a mí que
has blocked me but you ask him for
me tiene bloqueado pero ustedes pedirle
explanations there is here regarding this and
explicaciones hay aquí respecto a esto y
to ask him hey there is here this person is
de preguntarle oye hay aquí esta persona
going to be shot
va a ser baleada
this person is going to be shot from
esta persona va a ser baleado de
marbella bites or this toxicity if you
marbella bites o esta toxicidad si te
like from here not only that he invites
gusta de aquí ya no solamente que invita
people with toxicity
a la gente con toxicidad
and the question would be he is going to ban him for
y la pregunta sería lo va a banear por
bringing toxicity and not only for
traer la toxicidad y no solamente por
bringing toxicity but he said
traer la toxicidad sino que el dijo que
jokes about pedophilia and racism and
chistes de pedofilia y de racismo y de
things like that banned in one go do you remember in
cosas así baneado del tirón acordáis en
the debate
el debate
my mother and dude has done one it is
madre mía y tiparraco la ha hecho una es
an interview with this man it is
una entrevista a este hombre
the first time what
es la primera vez lo
the cuchos life those hard ones
que los cuchos la vida esos los duros
I have seen this miniature a thousand times I have
yo he visto mil veces esta miniatura he
seen this miniature a thousand times but
visto mil veces esta miniatura pero
I am always wrong because I believe that it
siempre me equivoco porque me creo que
is lol hito in the miniature it looks like
es lol hito en la miniatura se parece a
the liter dude and I always believe that the
lo litro tío y siempre me creo que el
lolito
lolito
come on let's start he is a person that I really
venga vamos a empezar es una persona que
want to interview  of bolt that
me apetece mucho entrevistar de bolt que
follows mister ego is a rapper known
sigue míster ego es un rapero conocido
for throwing crude remarks in his battles and he
por tirar crudezas en sus batallas y se
spends his time trying to create controversy not even in
la pasa intentando crear polémica ni en
the rap world they want
el mundo de rap lo quieren
to see him. He has a million views on the
a ver tiene un millón de visitas la
interview of this guy, I mean, the
entrevista de este tiparraco o sea el
guy will they know him from there, I can't imagine,
tipo lo conocerán por ahí no me imagino
no,
no
look, here he is also with molly, he
mira aquí está también con molly
is some people, I mean,
es una gente es decir
basically that is what
básicamente eso es por lo que se conoce
I am known for being on a separate board for
a mí estar en un tablero aparte por
violation of the offense man, the guy
vulneración de la ofensa tío el tío
criticizes
crítica
Dallas among some three that we have
a dallas entre algunos three que hemos
seen, there
vistos no
were not many thanks that you have to see
hubo muchísimas gracias que hay que ver
that giving them here proof of the videos and
que darlas acá prueba de los vídeos y
makes a video and how toxic he is and how heavy he is
hace vídeo y que tóxico es y qué pesado
no and now he recognizes here in the
es no y ahora él reconoce aquí en la
interview that he is a
entrevista que él es un
and basically that is why he is a
y básicamente eso es por lo que es un
rapper who insults people he
rapero que insulta a la gente
is a guy who is dedicated to insulting
es un tío que se dedica a insultar a
people for money he moves you see the south he is
gente por dinero mueve veis el sur es
very controversial known in the world of
muy polémico conocido en el mundo de las
battles he is always involved in some
batallas siempre está metido en alguna
controversy yes yes it is seen that it is seen that he is
polémica sí sí se ve que se ve que
known but it seems to me a walking lack of
conocido es pero me parece una falta de
respect
respeto andante
I hope that she takes action on the
yo espero que ella tome cartas en el
matter not her  remuneration of the and
asunto no la remuneración de los y
basically that's what
básicamente eso es por lo que se conoce
mister is known for but apart from that he's a rapper
a míster pero aparte pues es un rapero
who makes his lyrics to thieves or not
que hace su letritas a ladrones o no
because it's like manha this is a
porque como que da manha este es un
contest to keep more money I don't
concurso para quedarte más dinero no me
know the story very well but this is
sé muy bien la historia pero esto es
real let's see everyone who calls
real a ver todo el mundo que le llama
someone a thief it's because they're missing something
ladrón a alguien es porque le falta algo
okay so in this case to the people what
vale entonces en este caso a la gente lo
you're missing from here okay because
que te falta desde aquí vale porque no
I'm not professionally dedicated to the act mania
me dedico profesionalmente al acto manía
okay so there
vale
was an event in 2014 that
entonces hubo un evento en 2014 que
look where the story is going and it's
fíjate para dónde viene la historia y
called the hypnotic and I reached
que se llama el hipnótico y yo llegué a
the final with design and there was 800 euros in
la final con diseño y había 800 euros de
prize money
premio
okay so we said from 400 and
vale entonces dijimos de partir de 400 y
400 with them when they deposited the
400 con ellos cuando ingresaron el
prize they were going to evict me from my house
premio a mí me iban a deshauciar de casa
because I've been emancipated for
porque yo llevo emancipado de los
four years so I made up a
cuatros años pues me inventé una pedazo
huge lie that if the
de [__] como un castillo que si los
banks don't pay yes I don't know that on top of that
bancos no pagan que sí no sé que encima
he asked the one who in his that is a bit what to
le pedía al que en su que es un poco lo
make me a proof that he
que me hiciera un justificante de como
had paid him because it was
que le había pagado porque era diseñador
graphic designer well made a mess man
gráfico bueno hizo una bola tío
in short you kept the basic pasta
en resumen te quedaste la pasta básica
without warning
sin avisar
and when the 800 came in because they
y cuando ingresaron los 800 porque
charge that then the prize is paid
cargan eso entonces el premio se ingresa
to me instead of saying mass for rent
a mí en vez de decirle misa de alquiler
and well we are in a super hard war
y bueno estamos en una guerra súper dura
and I received a lot of
y yo recibí un montón de apaleamiento
public beating in which he was a thief for
público en los que era un ladrón para
all Christ of
todo cristo
course of course on top of that cause what was
claro claro encima causa lo que fue
deserved as such and there is no need for
merecido como tal y no hace falta haber
much more from this man or rather as
mucho más de este hombre o sea
the saying was like that saying that
como era el dicho como el dicho ese que
we like so much the strength of his
nos gusta tanto la fortaleza de su
grievance shows the weakness of your
agravio demuestra la debilidad de tu
argument not something like that was not what they
argumento no algo así era no lo que
said no but come on not years ago who
decían no pero vamos no hace años quien
wants but who can and coming from
quiere sino quien puede y viniendo de
this guy well the truth is I would
este tipo pues la verdad
n't be worried it would affect me with
tampoco me preocuparía me afectaría a
that nonsense that he said in the song
esa burrada que ha dicho en la canción
okay it seems very bad to me as a person lack
vale me parece muy mal me persona falta
of respect what are we going to have an opinion on that what are we going to have an opinion on
de respeto que vamos a opinar de eso que
no I think that
vamos a opinar no yo creo que eso a todo
everyone whether you like it or not
el mundo te caiga bien o te caiga mal da
we agree that this guy
la estamos de acuerdo en que este tipo
what he has done the song was a lack of
lo que ha hecho la canción una falta de
respect and a gratuitous insult and a
respeto y un insulto gratuito y una
very very serious accusation
pulsación muy muy grave una acusación
very serious and very ugly totally free so
muy grave y muy fea totalmente gratuita
why are we going to give it back
entonces para qué le vamos a la vuelta
importance of yes two times it seems
importancia de sí dos tiempos me parece
good to me it seems bad to me it seems disgusting to
bien me parece mal me parece repugnante
me it seems disgusting okay but seeing
me parece repugnante vale pero ya viendo
a little the type of the type of person or
un poco el tipo de el tipo de persona o
character they do not hide behind a character we do not
de personaje no se escudan un personaje
know no but seeing a little
no lo sabemos no pero ya viendo un poco
what he does and how he
a lo que se dedica y como él mismo se
defines himself not that I dedicate myself to messing with
define no que me dedico a meterme con la
people insulting people to earn
gente insultar a la gente para ganar
money well why do we want more why do we
dinero pues para qué queremos más para
want more of that yes yes what I would
qué queremos más a eso sí eso sí yo lo
do with twitter it is very
que sí haría lo de twitter es muy
services choosing because this type of
servicios escogiendo porque este tipo de
gets scary
entra miedo
I imagine no if he does not have it let's
me imagino no si no la tiene vamos
take the parents and all the
que [__] a los papis y todos los
kids okay and you start putting their
chavales vale y empiezas a poner sus
faces there on his twitter account when
caras ahí en su cuenta de twitter cuando
he is a public figure the others have not
él es un personaje público los otros no
marked their total because he only
se ha marcando su total porque sólo lo
did it well and you also remember since he
hacía bien y tú también os acordáis ya
had to take photos of people in
que tenía que [__] fotos de personas en
that interview he says that arca does not get involved
esa entrevista dice que arca no se mete
in the white and he says it as if it were the
de la blanca y lo dice como si fuese lo
most normal thing to talk about
más normal hablar de los problemas
personal problems that it is
personales que es
hopefully a  day eat a good one these are
ojalá un día se coma una buena éstos son
the people who have to eat good
la gente que se tienen que comer buenas
lawsuits man these are the people who have to
demandas tío estos son la gente se tiene
eat good lawsuits and who would have a long
que comer buenas demandas y que tendrían
way to go and well but about
recorrido además y bueno pero lo de
putting the anonymous kids in the
poner a los chavales anónimos a los
deposits and it seems incredible to me okay but
pósitos y me parece increíble vale pero
I especially good seeing the type of
yo sobre todo buenos viendo el tipo de
person that I won't pay much
persona que tampoco le echaré mucha
attention to it but the one I would pay attention to
cuenta pero yo a quien sí le echaría
would be there here the one who would be
cuenta sería hay aquí
noticed would be
a quien se le echaría cuenta sería ya
here and I would say today here the
aquí y le diría hoy haya aquí la
toxicity was not going outside hey here this was not
toxicidad no iba afuera oye aquí esto no
going to be manageable
iba manejable
this was not manageable here because if they are
esto no era manejable ya aquí porque si
not going to do it here 6 thank you
ya aquí no lo van ea 6
very much thank you very much
muchísimas gracias muchísimas gracias
one thing that she can handle here
una cosa que ella aquí lo pueda manejar
but maybe she put him in and she is going to and she is not going to
pero tal vez lo haya metido y va y no lo
want to kick him out
va a querer echar
but if he does something variable it does not matter that
pero si hace algo variable da igual que
the father puts him in
lo meta el papá
and that he has literally accused of
y que literalmente ha acusado de
sleeping with minors or something about
acostarse con menores o de algo de
minors to a kid who is
menores a un chaval que nos está
putting us in the series that he is
metiendo en la serie que nos está
putting us in with none of them right now there
metiendo con ninguno de ellos ahora
are no excuses there are no excuses
mismo ya no hay excusas no hay excusas
like jackie is not going to even this person on the
como jackie no va ni a esta persona del
server once again it is demonstrated what it is
servidor una vez más queda demostrado lo
worth a  once again and I get the
que es vale una vez más y me da la
feeling that's what's going to
sensación de que va a ser eso lo que va
happen I get the feeling in that
a pasar me da la sensación en esa
interview he says he's dedicated to buying
entrevista dice que se dedica a comprar
properties when everyone knows that he
propiedades cuando todos saben que de él
doesn't get paid that much in the rap world
un mundo del rap no se cobra tanto como
for that, even several freestylers
para eso incluso varios freestyler
came out and said that it was impossible
salieron a decir que eso era imposible
he's well known for being a loudmouth
es muy conocido por ser un bocachancla
well the thing is let's see how he acts and
bueno el caso vamos a ver cómo actúa y
here because I think I get the feeling
aquí porque yo creo me da la sensación
that here he's going to be the deaf one he's going to
de que ya aquí se va a ser el sordo va a
try to change the subject tomorrow and he's going to
intentar mañana cambiar de tema y va a
try to turn a blind eye to this issue
intentar hacerse el ciego en este tema
okay
vale
if he does something and takes measures it's going to be because of
si hace algo y toma medidas va a ser por
the pressure from the people who bet
la presión de la gente que apostamos
kids who bet and well guys
chavales que apostamos y bueno chicos